{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Shed, Barn \u0026 Playhouse Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/43280/":{"taskOID":43280,"originalTaskOID":43280,"setID":769,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4482,"questionDisplayText":"Repairs Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs to be repaired?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2791,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"General repairs","answerDisplayText":"General repairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5129,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remodel or enlarge","answerDisplayText":"Remodel or enlarge","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":643,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Add or move walls","answerDisplayText":"Add or move walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":624,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Add electricity","answerDisplayText":"Add electricity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":648,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Add plumbing","answerDisplayText":"Add plumbing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5228,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Repair siding","answerDisplayText":"Repair siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5226,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Repair roofing","answerDisplayText":"Repair roofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":644,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Add or move windows","answerDisplayText":"Add or move windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5686,"questionDisplayText":"Building Use","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the building used for?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6112,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Storage","answerDisplayText":"Storage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":949,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Barn","answerDisplayText":"Barn","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7120,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Workshop","answerDisplayText":"Workshop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4731,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Playhouse","answerDisplayText":"Playhouse","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2881,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Guest House","answerDisplayText":"Guest House","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4335,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Office","answerDisplayText":"Office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4480,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Outbuilding","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of barn, shed, or playhouse do you have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood -- traditionally constructed","answerDisplayText":"Wood -- traditionally constructed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6072,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Steel framed","answerDisplayText":"Steel framed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4868,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Pre-manufactured","answerDisplayText":"Pre-manufactured","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":869,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Assembled from kit","answerDisplayText":"Assembled from kit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6715,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Vinyl siding","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1747,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Custom","answerDisplayText":"Custom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":10,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4482,"questionDisplayText":"Repairs Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs to be repaired?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2791,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"General repairs","answerDisplayText":"General repairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5129,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remodel or enlarge","answerDisplayText":"Remodel or enlarge","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":643,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Add or move walls","answerDisplayText":"Add or move walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":624,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Add electricity","answerDisplayText":"Add electricity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":648,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Add plumbing","answerDisplayText":"Add plumbing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5228,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Repair siding","answerDisplayText":"Repair siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5226,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Repair roofing","answerDisplayText":"Repair roofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":644,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Add or move windows","answerDisplayText":"Add or move windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2791,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"General repairs","answerDisplayText":"General repairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5129,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remodel or enlarge","answerDisplayText":"Remodel or enlarge","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":643,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Add or move walls","answerDisplayText":"Add or move walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":624,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Add electricity","answerDisplayText":"Add electricity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":648,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Add plumbing","answerDisplayText":"Add plumbing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5228,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Repair siding","answerDisplayText":"Repair siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5226,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Repair roofing","answerDisplayText":"Repair roofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":644,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Add or move windows","answerDisplayText":"Add or move windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5686,"questionDisplayText":"Building Use","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the building used for?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6112,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Storage","answerDisplayText":"Storage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":949,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Barn","answerDisplayText":"Barn","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7120,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Workshop","answerDisplayText":"Workshop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4731,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Playhouse","answerDisplayText":"Playhouse","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2881,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Guest House","answerDisplayText":"Guest House","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4335,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Office","answerDisplayText":"Office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6112,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Storage","answerDisplayText":"Storage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":949,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Barn","answerDisplayText":"Barn","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7120,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Workshop","answerDisplayText":"Workshop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4731,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Playhouse","answerDisplayText":"Playhouse","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2881,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Guest House","answerDisplayText":"Guest House","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4335,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Office","answerDisplayText":"Office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4480,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Outbuilding","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of barn, shed, or playhouse do you have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood -- traditionally constructed","answerDisplayText":"Wood -- traditionally constructed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6072,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Steel framed","answerDisplayText":"Steel framed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4868,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Pre-manufactured","answerDisplayText":"Pre-manufactured","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":869,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Assembled from kit","answerDisplayText":"Assembled from kit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6715,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Vinyl siding","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1747,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Custom","answerDisplayText":"Custom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood -- traditionally constructed","answerDisplayText":"Wood -- traditionally constructed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6072,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Steel framed","answerDisplayText":"Steel framed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4868,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Pre-manufactured","answerDisplayText":"Pre-manufactured","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":869,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Assembled from kit","answerDisplayText":"Assembled from kit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6715,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Vinyl siding","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1747,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Custom","answerDisplayText":"Custom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":10,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/43280/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":43280,"taskName":"Shed, Barn or Playhouse - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair a Shed, Barn or Playhouse","xmTaskDescriptor":"Shed, Barn \u0026 Playhouse Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1709,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Play Playhouse Barn steel free","textMessagingName":"Repr Barn","rolloverLongDesc":"Typically only available in agricultural communities.  This category is not for converting barns to dwellings, offices and studios. That would be covered under the remodeling categories.","rolloverShortDesc":"Specialist in restoring large outbuildings.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair a Shed, Barn or Playhouse.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Storage Shed Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fix a Barn or Shed Roof, Playhouse, etc.","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":9,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Shed, Barn or Playhouse Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Shed, Barn or Playhouse - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Shed, Barn or Playhouse Project","urlName":"Shed-Barn-or-Playhouse-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Shed \u0026 Barn Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor | Repair Shed/Barn Roof","searchKeywords":"Play,Playhouse,Barn,outbuilding,out,freestanding,Shed,enclosure, kids, play, house, childrens","emcCategoryOid":-12063,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":769,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}